CHRISTINE ONG

JUNIOR SOFTWARE TESTER

CONTACT

+63 928 253 9101

 \checkmark

tinongfb@gmail.com

2

Quezon City, PH

LINKS

LINKEDIN

GITHUB

MY PERSONAL PAGE

SKILLS

Manual Testing

Blackbox/Functionality Testing

Mobile App Testing

JIRA

API Testing

Problem-Solving

Computer Literacy

LICENSE

PROFESSIONAL FOOD TECHNOLOGIST: License number 0000631

EDUCATION

BS FOOD TECHNOLOGY

University of the Philippines, Diliman

2009 - 2014

SUMMARY

I am a manual QA Engineer with 2 years of experience in test case creation and thorough execution of black-box and functionality tests. I have knowledge in basic Java and SQL. I aim to expand my skills and also learn Automation testing while upholding software quality through QA.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

JUNIOR MANUAL ENGINEER, QA

Softwares Ventures, Inc.

Oct 2021 - Present

- Creating and refining Test Cases of various tools and web applications
- Functional and GUI testing of web applications in various browsers in Windows and their adaptability in mobile browsers (Android OS)
- Testing of batch programs in centOS (includes database management through SQL)
- Testing of mobile applications integrated with a web application and database (Cassandra)
- API testing using Postman
- Verification of resolved issues
- Part of Agile setup daily scrum, JIRA kanban board management and poker planning
- Deployment of applications in Payara; deployment of docker images through terminal
- Underwent basic Java training and basic SQL and database management training

TECHNICAL SPECIALIST (FOOD INGREDIENTS)

Promax International Corporation

2016 - 2021

 Created various food sample prototypes (for the purpose of showcasing the company's functional food ingredients); food product innovation through sensory evaluation and discussion